♪♪♪
♪ I'VE BEEN TRYNA CALL ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN ON MY
OWN FOR LONG ENOUGH ♪
♪ MAYBE YOU CAN SHOW
ME HOW TO LOVE, MAYBE ♪
♪ I'M GOING
THROUGH WITHDRAWALS ♪
♪ YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE TO DO TOO MUCH ♪
♪ YOU CAN TURN ME ON
WITH JUST A TOUCH, BABY ♪
♪ I LOOK AROUND AND ♪
♪ SIN CITY'S COLD AND EMPTY
(OH) ♪
♪ NO ONE'S AROUND TO JUDGE ME
♪ I CAN'T SEE
CLEARLY WHEN YOU'RE GONE ♪
♪ I SAID, OOH, I'M
BLINDED BY THE LIGHTS ♪
♪ NO, I CAN'T SLEEP
UNTIL I FEEL YOUR TOUCH ♪
♪ I SAID, OOH, I'M
DROWNING IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ OH, WHEN I'M LIKE THIS,
YOU'RE THE ONE I TRUST ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'M RUNNING OUT OF TIME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I CAN SEE THE
SUN LIGHT UP THE SKY ♪
♪ SO I HIT THE ROAD
IN OVERDRIVE, BABY, OH ♪
♪ THE CITY'S COLD AND EMPTY
(OH) ♪
♪ NO ONE'S AROUND TO JUDGE ME
♪ I CAN'T SEE
CLEARLY WHEN YOU'RE GONE ♪
♪ I SAID, OOH, I'M
BLINDED BY THE LIGHTS ♪
♪ NO, I CAN'T SLEEP
UNTIL I FEEL YOUR TOUCH ♪
♪ I SAID, OOH, I'M
DROWNING IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ OH, WHEN I'M LIKE THIS,
YOU'RE THE ONE I TRUST ♪
♪ I'M JUST CALLING
BACK TO LET YOU KNOW
(BACK TO LET YOU KNOW) ♪
♪ I COULD NEVER SAY IT ON THE
PHONE (SAY IT ON THE PHONE) ♪
♪ WILL NEVER LET YOU
GO THIS TIME (OOH) ♪
♪ I SAID, OOH, I'M
BLINDED BY THE LIGHTS ♪
♪ NO, I CAN'T SLEEP
UNTIL I FEEL YOUR TOUCH ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I SAID, OOH, I'M
BLINDED BY THE LIGHTS ♪
♪ NO, I CAN'T SLEEP
UNTIL I FEEL YOUR TOUCH ♪